I'm
leaving my
little home for a while.  So,
in preparation, I gathered the
last remnants of
the harvest.  I managed to
get some potatoes
and carrots from my
father's garden, and
also planted some lilies
that
my
mother-in-law so kindly suggested.  My garden
and plot are still a long way
from the fabulous
place I imagine,
but it's so exciting
to start this process.
I always remember that
saying: "The best
time to plant a tree
was 20 years ago."
The second best time
is today."  Does
n't this apply to
our goals as well?
We may regret not
pursuing them sooner,
but now is the
best time to start
again.  I will miss
you all while
I am gone.  Maybe the
frost will hit before I get back,
but I'll be back soon
.
The day was so
peaceful, but as soon as I
turned on
the camera, almost
every dog ​​in the area
started barking.  Hi
, I wanted to make a
very short, but
hopefully enjoyable
video about me
going away for a while.  I won't be there
, but I will
definitely be
back.  Luke and I
are trying
to get ourselves a
little vacation
for a few days to
celebrate our
honeymoon, which
we weren't able to do
in May when we
got married.  We both
went to work the
Monday after the
wedding.  We
got married on Saturday,
went to work on Monday
, and we just didn't have a
chance to
take some time
for ourselves, so now we're
going to the coast,
visit his
aunt, and hopefully
stay at a really
cute
bed and breakfast,
which I hope
to share with you
when I get back,
unpack, and
get back to normal
.  We are
celebrating
our engagement anniversary, and we are
also just happy that
we are together,
healthy, and happy.  I was
constantly in and out
of
the hospital,
and this
cycle of visits to
doctors continues, so it's
a little tiring,
sometimes frustrating, but
what is is, and that's why I
really appreciate the opportunity now to
go somewhere, breathe
fresh air,
continue my journey
to healing, and I'm really looking forward to
it.  It's so
important to be grateful
and truly love and
appreciate every moment,
because you never know what
life will have in store for
you in the next
minute.  I really
always miss
filming my videos
when I'm away, so
I wanted to
do at least something
small now,
even though
I'm short on time
this week before the
meeting.  I send you
all my love.
Thank you again for all your
kind words and
messages.  This
means a lot to me, and we'll
see each other very
soon.  Take care of yourself.
See you later.